{
    "subject": "resource/Wayland_(village),_New_York",
    "predicate": "ontology/areaCode",
    "object": "585",
    "human_readable": "The area code of Wayland (village), New York is 585.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8904966115951538,
            "question": "What is the area code for Wayland, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.730660080909729,
            "question": "Are there any other places in New York with the same area code as Wayland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.711264967918396,
            "question": "What number represents the area code for Wayland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.580410897731781,
            "question": "Is Wayland a city or village?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5003609657287598,
            "question": "In which state is Wayland located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4699210822582245,
            "question": "If you were calling someone in Wayland, what area code would you dial?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1593243032693863,
            "question": "What other information might be useful to know besides the area code when making a call?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10855018347501755,
            "question": "How can you identify the location of a phone call using an area code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10446719825267792,
            "question": "What is the significance of an area code in telecommunications?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09265847504138947,
            "question": "How does an area code help with telephone routing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The area code of Wayland (village), New York is 585.",
            "html": "dbpedia_45_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of an area code in telecommunications?",
            "html": "dbpedia_45_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can you identify the location of a phone call using an area code?",
            "html": "dbpedia_45_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other information might be useful to know besides the area code when making a call?",
            "html": "dbpedia_45_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_45_133.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_45_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_45_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_45_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_45_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_45_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_45_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_45_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_45_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_45_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that the area code for Wayland, NY is 585. Therefore, the statement \"The area code of Wayland (village), New York is 585\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}